Finding Aid for University of Michigan Class Albums
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- 1874 Class Album
  - Student Groups
    - Student Group (Box 27)
    - Class of 1873 (Box 27)
    - Class of 1874 (Box 27)
      [150]
    - Class of 1875 (Box 27)
    - Class of 1876 (Box 27)
    - Class of 1877 (Box 27)
    - Student Group (Box 27)
    - Chronicle Staff (Box 27)
    - Baseball Team (Box 27)
    - Student Group (Box 27)
    - Ann Arbor Scenes (Box 27)
    - Looking North on State Street, Methodist Church Steeple in Distance (Box 27)
    - Looking South on State Street, Methodist Church in Foreground (Box 27)
    - West Huron Street, Looking West from State Street toward Main (Box 27)
    - Birdseye View of Ann Arbor (Box 27)
    - First Methodist Church (Box 27)
      [158]
    - Presbyterian Church (Box 27)
    - Huron River (Box 27)
- 1874 Class Album (copy 2) (Box 28)
  [The album is in poor repair, and many pictures are missing.]
- 1875 Class Album
  - Faculty
    - Adams, Charles Kendall (Box 29)
    - Angell, James Burrill (Box 29)
    - Baker Marcus (Box 29)
    - Beman: Wooster Woodruff (Box 29)
    - Bullock, Dillman (Box 29)
    - Campbell, James Cowan (Box 29)
    - Campbell James Valentine (Box 29)
    - Church, (Prof.?) (Box 29)
    - Cocker, Rev. Benjamin Franklin (Box 29)
    - Cooley, Thomas McIntyre (Box 29)
    - D'Ooge, Rev. Martin Luther (Box 29)
    - Douglas, Silas Hamilton (Box 29)
    - Dunster, Edward Swift (Box 29)
    - Frieze, Henry Simmons (Box 29)
    - Frothingham,George Edward (Box 29)
    - Gerrish, Frederick Henry (Box 29)
    - Greene, Charles Ezra (Box 29)
    - Haven, Rev. Erastus Otis (Box 29)
    - Hilgard, Eugene Woldemar (Box 29)
    - Harrington, Mark Walrod (Box 29)
    - Irving, Pierre Leslie (Box 29)
    - Johnson, Otis Coe (Box 29)
    - Kent, Charles Artemas (Box 29)
    - MacLean, Donald (Box 29)
    - Merriman, George Benjamin (Box 29)
    - Morris, George Sylvester (Box 29)
    - Olney, Edward (Box 29)
    - Palmer, Alonzo Benjamin (Box 29)
    - Pattengill, Albert Henderson (Box 29)
    - Prescott, Albert Benjamin (Box 29)
    - Rose, Preston Benjamin (Box 29)
    - Sager, Abram (Box 29)
    - Tappan, Rev. Henry Philip (Box 29)
    - Ten Brook, Rev. Andrew (Box 29)
    - Tyler, Moses Coit (Box 29)
    - Walter, Charles Irish (Box 29)
    - Walter, Edward Lorraine (Box 29)
    - Watson, James Craig (Box 29)
    - Wells, William Palmer (Box 29)
    - Williams, Rev. George Palmer (Box 29)
    - Winchell, Alexander (Box 29)
    - Wood, DeVolson (Box 29)
    - DePont, Paul R.B. (Box 29)
    - Hannequin, Alfred (Box 29)
    - Scott, Frank Austin (Box 29)
  - Members of the class
    - Abbott, George Hazelton (Box 29)
    - Anderson, San Louie (Box 29)
    - Andrews, Emma Cornelia (Box 29)
    - Andrews, Samuel Chester (Box 29)
    - Angle, Martha (Box 29)
    - Arey, Albert Llewellyn (Box 29)
    - Baker, Lucius (Box 29)
    - Baldwin, Charles Cutler (Box 29)
    - Ball, Frank Webster (Box 29)
    - Barnhart, Irving Willis (Box 29)
    - Barrett, James Madison (Box 29)
    - Bates, Henry David (Box 29)
    - Bigelow, William Francis (Box 29)
    - Birdsall, Ben (Box 29)
    - Bixby, David Alonzo (Box 29)
    - Blackburn, Hiram Powell ? (Box 29)
    - Briggs, George Allen (Box 29)
    - Brotherton, Williard Irving (Box 29)
    - Buckingham, Charles Luman (Box 29)
    - Bulkley, Frederick Groendycke (Box 29)
    - Burch, Charles Sumner (Box 29)
    - Burris, John Fletcher (Box 29)
    - Burt, Benjamin Chapman (Box 29)
    - Burt, William Wadsworth (Box 29)
    - Burton, Charles Francis orTatem (Box 29)
    - Carnefix, Charles Alexander (Box 29)
    - Carpenter, Rolla Clinton (Box 29)
    - Chapin, Angie Clara (Box 29)
    - Clark, Charles Whitefield (Box 29)
    - Clark, William Rice (Box 29)
    - Cook, Emily Persis (Box 29)
    - Cook, Norman Philip (Box 29)
    - Corwin, George Whipple (Box 29)
    - Culver, Frank H. (Box 29)
    - Cushing, Rolla Tileston (Box 29)
    - Davis, Lorenzo (Box 29)
      [45 or 86]
    - Davis, Samuel Benjamin (Box 29)
      [45 or86]
    - Denison, Amos (Box 29)
    - Dickinson, Leman Lee (Box 29)
    - Dorsett, Charles William (Box 29)
    - Doty, William George (Box 29)
    - Eaton, James Clement (Box 29)
    - Fall, Delos (Box 29)
    - Field, Charles Fred (Box 29)
    - Fletcher, Frank Ward (Box 29)
    - Fletcher, Lorenzo Varnum (Box 29)
    - Fleming, Clara A. (Box 29)
    - Ford, Horatio Clark (Box 29)
    - Fox, Charles (Box 29)
    - Fox, George Ludlow (Box 29)
    - Gelston, William Fanning (Box 29)
    - Gilchrist, Charles Pierce (Box 29)
    - Graber, Thomas Frederick (Box 29)
    - Grant, EmersonWarren (Box 29)
    - Gumaer, Adelbert George (Box 29)
    - Hahn, Henry Harrison (Box 29)
    - Harris, Charles Taylor (Box 29)
      [132 or 139]
    - Harris, Frederick Walter (Box 29)
    - Heyser, Walter Jacob (Box 29)
    - Hoover, Joseph Warren (Box 29)
    - Hosmer, George Stedman (Box 29)
    - Hubbard, Caroline Irene (Box 29)
    - Hutchins, Eugene Ralph (Box 29)
    - Jacobs, Charles Huntington (Box 29)
    - Jones, Ephraim (?) (Box 29)
    - Keeler, Bronson C. (Box 29)
    - Knowlton, Jerome Cyril (Box 29)
    - McGowan, Andrew Josiah (Box 29)
    - McMahon, James Benoin (Box 29)
    - McPherson, Leslie Combs (Box 29)
    - Miller, Willoughby Dayton (Box 29)
    - Mills, Edwin Lockwood (Box 29)
    - Mitchell, Irving Nelson (Box 29)
    - Morrison, John Henry (Box 29)
    - Newton, Martin Luther (Box 29)
    - Oakley, Dewitt Jay (Box 29)
    - Oakley Edwin Clarence (Box 29)
    - Oven, Arthur Gordon (Box 29)
    - Pantlind, George Evert (Box 29)
    - Parker Jonathan Willis (Box 29)
    - Parsons, Edward Ira (Box 29)
    - Pierson, Enos David (Box 29)
    - Platt, Frederick A. (Box 29)
    - Potter, William Hobart (Box 29)
    - Robeson, Henry John (Box 29)
    - Root, Edgar Dean (Box 29)
    - Roys, Herman Merton (Box 29)
    - Russel, Walter S. (Box 29)
    - Seelye, Alexander Hawks (Box 29)
    - Shafroth, John Franklin (Box 29)
    - Shepard, James Henry (Box 29)
    - Shepardson, Oscar Pliny (Box 29)
    - Smith, Stewart Whedon (Box 29)
    - Stellwagon, Augustus John Charles (Box 29)
    - Stewart, John Alexander (Box 29)
    - Stoddart, John Joseph (Box 29)
    - Taber, Lelia Alice (Box 29)
    - Taylor, Thomas Elwood (Box 29)
    - Thomas, Ella (Box 29)
    - Thomas, Willliam (Box 29)
    - Turner, Will C. (Box 29)
    - Upham, Horace Alonzo Jaques (Box 29)
    - Wells, James Dwight (Box 29)
    - Wells, Marcus Jonathan ? (Box 29)
    - Whitmore, Welles (Box 29)
    - Wilson, Percy Ripley (Box 29)
    - Winslow, Harriet Lavina (Box 29)
    - Wood, Franklin Pierce (Box 29)
    - Young, Abram Van Eps (Box 29)
  - Attended but not in the class
    - Laible, Edwin Forrest (Box 29)
    - Walker, Charles Hinsdale (Box 29)
  - Campus Personalitites
    - "Fritz" Janitor (Box 29)
    - "George" Janitor (Box 29)
    - "Jimmy" Postman (Box 29)
  - Campus Buildings and Views
    - Medical Building (Box 29)
      [173]
    - University Hall (Box 29)
      [171]
    - Ann Arbor General View (Box 29)
      [170]
    - University Hall Chapel (Box 29)
    - Haven Hall Walk past the Law Building (Box 29)
      [162]
    - University Hall--Statue Nydia ? (Box 29)
    - University Hall--Haven Hall (Box 29)
      [172]
    - Observatory (Box 29)
      [174]
    - President's House (Box 29)
      [175]
    - Engineering Class of 1875 (Box 29)
      [176]
    - Engineering Class of 1876 (Box 29)
    - Class of 1877 (Box 29)
    - Class of 1876 (Box 29)
    - Class of 1875 (Box 29)
      [167]
    - Class of 1874 (Box 29)
      [166]
    - Palladium Board (Box 29)
    - Baseball Club 1875 (Box 29)
- 1875 Class Album (Literary)
  - Professors
    - President Tappan (Box 30)
    - President Haven (Box 30)
    - President Angell (Box 30)
    - Dr. Cocker (Box 30)
    - Prof. Merriman (Box 30)
    - Dr.Williams (Box 30)
    - Prof. Olney (Box 30)
    - Prof. Watson (Box 30)
    - Prof. Winchell (Box 30)
    - Prof. Heilgard (Box 30)
    - Prof. Blackburn (Box 30)
    - Prof. Frieze (Box 30)
    - Prof. Hutchins (Box 30)
    - Moses Coit Tyler (Box 30)
    - Prof. DePont (Box 30)
    - Morris (Box 30)
    - Unidentified (Box 30)
    - Corwin (Box 30)
    - Prof. Ten Brook (Box 30)
    - Prof. Adams (Box 30)
    - Prof. Berman (Box 30)
    - Prof. Scott (Box 30)
    - Prof. Irving (Box 30)
    - Prof. Dennison (Box 30)
    - Prof. Ford (Box 30)
    - Douglas (Box 30)
    - Prof. Rose (Box 30)
    - Prof. Prescott (Box 30)
    - Prof. Johnson (Box 30)
    - Prof. Frothingham (Box 30)
    - Prof. Wood (Box 30)
    - Prof. Green (Box 30)
    - Prof. Campbell (Box 30)
    - Prof. Walker (Box 30)
    - Prof. Cooley (Box 30)
    - Prof. Church (Box 30)
  - Students
    - Abbott (Box 30)
    - Aldrich (Box 30)
    - Anderson (Box 30)
    - Andrews (Box 30)
    - Angle (Box 30)
    - Arey (Box 30)
    - Baker (Box 30)
    - Baldwin (Box 30)
    - Ball (Box 30)
    - Barnhart (Box 30)
    - Barrett (Box 30)
    - Bates (Box 30)
    - Bigelow (Box 30)
    - Birdsall (Box 30)
    - Bixby (Box 30)
    - Briggs (Box 30)
    - Brotherton (Box 30)
    - Buckingham (Box 30)
    - Bulkley (Box 30)
    - Burch (Box 30)
    - Burris (Box 30)
    - Burt (Box 30)
    - Carnefix (Box 30)
    - Carpenter (Box 30)
    - Chapin (Box 30)
    - Clark (Box 30)
    - Clark (Box 30)
    - Cook (Box 30)
    - Cook (Box 30)
    - Culver (Box 30)
    - Cushing (Box 30)
    - Davis (Box 30)
    - Dickinson (Box 30)
    - Dorsett (Box 30)
    - Doty (Box 30)
    - Eaton (Box 30)
    - Fall (Box 30)
    - Field (Box 30)
    - Fletcher (Box 30)
    - Fletcher (Box 30)
    - Ford (Box 30)
    - Fox (Box 30)
    - Fox (Box 30)
    - Gelston (Box 30)
    - Gilchrist (Box 30)
    - Graber (Box 30)
    - Grant (Box 30)
    - Gumaer (Box 30)
    - Hahn (Box 30)
    - Harris (Box 30)
    - Harris (Box 30)
    - Heyser (Box 30)
    - Hoover (Box 30)
    - Hosmer (Box 30)
    - Hubbard (Box 30)
    - Hutchings (Box 30)
    - Jacobs (Box 30)
    - Keeler (Box 30)
    - Knowlton (Box 30)
    - McGowen (Box 30)
    - McMahon (Box 30)
    - McPherson (Box 30)
    - Miller (Box 30)
    - Mills (Box 30)
    - Mitchell (Box 30)
    - Morrison (Box 30)
    - Newton (Box 30)
    - Oakley (Box 30)
    - Oakley (Box 30)
    - Oven (Box 30)
    - Pantlind (Box 30)
    - Parker (Box 30)
    - Parsons (Box 30)
    - Pierson (Box 30)
    - Platt (Box 30)
    - Potter (Box 30)
    - Robeson (Box 30)
    - Root (Box 30)
    - Roys (Box 30)
    - Russell (Box 30)
    - Seeley (Box 30)
    - Shafroth (Box 30)
    - Shepard (Box 30)
    - Shepardson (Box 30)
    - Smith (Box 30)
    - Stellwagen (Box 30)
    - Stewart (Box 30)
    - Stoddart (Box 30)
    - Tabon (Box 30)
    - Taylor (Box 30)
    - Thomas (Box 30)
    - Thomas (Box 30)
    - Turner (Box 30)
    - Upham (Box 30)
    - Watkins (Box 30)
    - Wells (Box 30)
    - Welles (Box 30)
    - Whitmore (Box 30)
    - Wilson (Box 30)
    - Winslow (Box 30)
    - Wood (Box 30)
    - Young (Box 30)
    - Andrews (Box 30)
    - Douglas (Box 30)
    - Bullock (Box 30)
    - Campbell (Box 30)
  - Personalities
    - Robert (Janitor) (Box 30)
    - Jimmie (Mail Carrier) (Box 30)
  - Buildings and Scenes
    - Ann Arbor (Box 30)
    - University Hall with old wings (Box 30)
    - Law Department (Box 30)
    - Walk leading past Law to University Building (Box 30)
    - N. W. Entrance to Campus and West State Street (Box 30)
    - Medical Department (Box 30)
    - Laboratory (Box 30)
    - Ave. leading past Law to Laboratory (Box 30)
    - Branch Ave. to S.E. Corner of Campus (Box 30)
    - Statue of Benjamin Franklin, Congregational Church on State Street (Box 30)
    - Huron St. looking West, Presbyterian Church on left (Box 30)
    - Laocoon and Two Sons (Box 30)
    - Observatory (Box 30)
    - Law Building and University Hall (Box 30)
    - Campus Walk leading to Chemical Laboratory (Box 30)
    - Class Stone (Box 30)
    - Baseball Club (Box 30)
      [161]
    - Engineers (Box 30)
    - Student group (Box 30)
    - Student group (Box 30)
- 1875 Class Album (partial)
  - 1875 Class Album (partial) (Box 30-a)
- 1875 Class Album
  - Faculty
    - Adams, Charles K., MA, Prof. History (Box 44)
    - Angell, James B., LLD, University President (Box 44)
    - Cocker, Benjamin F., DD, Prof. Mental and Moral Philosophy (Box 44)
    - Cooley, Judge Thomas E.,LLD, Prof. Law and Supreme Court Michigan Justice (Box 44)
    - Douglas, Silas H., MA MD, Prof. Chemistry (Box 44)
    - Frieze, Henry S., LLD, Prof. Latin Language and Literature (Box 44)
    - Hutchins, Harry B., MA, Assistant Prof. in History and English Language (Box 44)
    - Morris, George S., PHD, Prof. Modern Language and Literature (Box 44)
    - Olney, Edward A., LLD, Prof. Mathematics (Box 44)
    - Tyler, Moses C, LLD, Prof. English Language (Box 44)
    - Watson, James C., LLD, Prof. Astronomy (Box 44)
    - Winchell, Alexander, MA, Prof. Geology, Botany and Zoology (Box 44)
  - Members of the Class
    - Abbot, George H., PHB, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania (Box 44)
    - Avey, Albert L., CE, Whitewater, Wisconsin (Box 44)
    - Baker, Lucius, CE, Kalamazoo, Michigan, Class Treasurer (Box 44)
    - Baker, Marcus, MA, Assistant Prof. Math (Box 44)
    - Barch, Charles S., BA, Ann Arbor, Michigan, Class President (Box 44)
    - Barrett, James, M PHB, Arlington, Illinois (Box 44)
    - Buckingham, Charles S., CE, Berlin Heights, Ohio (Box 44)
    - Chapin, Angie C., BA, Flint, Michigan (Box 44)
    - Cushing, Rolla T., BA, Charlotte, Michigan (Box 44)
    - Dennison, Charles S., CE, Assistant Prof. Drawing and English (Box 44)
    - Dickinson, Leman L., CE, Grand Rapids, Michigan (Box 44)
    - Flemming, Clara A, Grand Rapids, Michigan (Box 44)
    - Hahn, Henry H., BA, Ann Arbor MI (Box 44)
    - Keeler, Bronson O., BA, Chicago, Illinois (Box 44)
    - Laible, Forrest E., Detroit, Michigan (Box 44)
    - MacGowan, Andrew J., PHB, Coldwater, Michigan (Box 44)
    - McMahon, James B., PHB, Manchester, Michigan (Box 44)
    - Mills, Edwin S., BS, Marshall, Michigan (Box 44)
    - Mitchell, Irving N., PHB, Niles, Michigan (Box 44)
    - Pantlind, George E., CE, Grand Rapids, Michigan (Box 44)
    - Parsons, Edward Ira, CE, Oberlin, Ohio (Box 44)
    - Seelye, Alexander H., BS, Hudson, Michigan (Box 44)
    - Unidentified Woman (Box 44)
    - Unidentified Woman (Box 44)
    - Unidentified Woman (Box 44)
    - Wilson, Percy R, PHB, Columbus, Ohio (Box 44)
    - Winslow, Harriet S., BS, Kalamazoo, Michigan (Box 44)
- 1876 Class Album (Pharmacy)
  - Faculty
    - Angell, James Burrill (Box 31)
    - Cheever, Henry Sylvester (Box 31)
      (6)
    - Douglass, Sam T. (Box 31)
      (9)
    - Douglas, Silas Hamilton (Box 31)
      (3)
    - Harrington, Nick Walrod (Box 31)
      (4)
    - Johnson, Otis Coe (Box 31)
      (7)
    - Pettee, William Henry (Box 31)
      (8)
    - Prescott, Albert Benjamin (Box 31)
      (2)
    - Rose, Preston Benjamin (Box 31)
      (5)
    - Vaughn, Victor Clarence (Box 31)
      (10)
  - Students
    - Allen, Samuel E. (Box 31)
      (16)
    - Ames, Joseph Henry (Box 31)
      (12)
    - Beach. Lyman Fowler (Box 31)
      (17)
    - Bower, Francis Thomas (Box 31)
      (13)
    - Buckham, James Neelands (Box 31)
      (18)
    - Burroughs, Charles Silvers (Box 31)
      (19)
    - Churchill, Orrin Landsford (Box 31)
      (20)
    - Clark, John Thaddeus (Box 31)
      (21)
    - Coughlin, Jeremiah (Box 31)
      (22)
    - Dietrich, Charles Wallace Llewellyn (Box 31)
      (23)
    - Dingley, Charles Austin (Box 31)
      (15)
    - Eddy, Charles Hulbert (Box 31)
      (24)
    - Fuller, Louis C. (Box 31)
      (25)
    - Green, Morris Udeen (Box 31)
      (26)
    - Grimwood, Charles (Box 31)
      (27)
    - Gundrum, George (Box 31)
      (28)
    - Holloway, William John (Box 31)
      (29)
    - James, Henry Fennell (Box 31)
      (30)
    - Little, John Robbins (Box 31)
      (31)
    - Lynn, James (Box 31)
      (32)
    - Massey, Frank William Herbert (Box 31)
      (33)
    - Morgan, James William (Box 31)
      (34)
    - Parsons, Henry Betts (Box 31)
      (14)
    - Pierron, Joseph John (Box 31)
      (35)
    - Risser, Edward Judson (Box 31)
      (36)
    - Roys, Herman Merton (Box 31)
      (37)
    - Sheffield, William Clarence (Box 31)
      (38)
    - Stewart, Thomas Martin (Box 31)
      (39)
    - Watson. Catherine M. (Box 31)
      (40)
    - Whitlark, Walter John (Box 31)
      (41)
  - In the School
    - Arnold, Lynn Delevan (Box 31)
      (42)
    - Condon, Mike ? (Janitor) (Box 31)
      (44)
    - Sweetser, Franklin Eugene (Box 31)
      (43)
- 1876 Class Album
  - Faculty
    - Angell, James B. (Box 32)
    - Cocker, Benjamin F. (Box 32)
    - Morris, George S. (Box 32)
    - Olney, Edward (Box 32)
    - Harrington, Mark W. (Box 32)
    - Scott, Frank Austin (Box 32)
  - Students
    - Andrews, Lucy C. (Box 32)
    - Baker, George S. (Box 32)
    - Bellis, Ida M. (Mrs. A.W. Ryan) (Box 32)
    - Colby, Vine (Box 32)
    - Eaglesfield, Elizabeth (Box 32)
    - Ekin, Annie Warden (Mrs. A.H. Pattengill) (Box 32)
    - Farrand, Helen (Box 32)
    - Floyd, John C. (Box 32)
    - Gustin, Fred Keays (Box 32)
    - Hall, Abram S. (Box 32)
    - Mason, Gertrude H. (Box 32)
    - Pearson, Albert C. (Box 32)
    - Reed, Louisa M. (Mrs. C.H. Stowell) (Box 32)
    - Stanley, Louis Crandall (Box 32)
    - Stockbridge, Emma S. (Mrs. T.W. Ellison) (Box 32)
    - Watterson, James A. (Box 32)
    - Woolridge, Charles W. (Box 32)
  - Others
    - Unidentified (Box 32)
      [25-28, 30-31,]
    - Farnsworth (Box 32)
    - Pitts, Myrtle (Box 32)
    - Wood, Norman A. (Box 32)
    - Wood, Anna E. (Box 32)
    - Taylor, Louise (Box 32)
    - Wood, Dwight Leonard (Box 32)
    - Wood, Marcia (Box 32)
    - Wood, Maria (Scott) (Box 32)
- 1876 Class Album
  - Faculty
    - Angell, James B. (Box 33)
    - D'Ooge, Martin L. (Box 33)
    - Unidentified (Box 33)
    - Cocker, Benjamin.F.. (Box 33)
    - Olney, Edward. (Box 33)
    - Winchell, Alexander (Box 33)
    - Williams, George P.. (Box 33)
    - Tyler, Moses C.. (Box 33)
    - Adams, Charles K.. (Box 33)
    - Unidentified. (Box 33)
    - Steere, J.B.. (Box 33)
    - Frieze, H.L.. (Box 33)
    - Campbell, James V.. (Box 33)
    - Cooley, Thomas M.. (Box 33)
    - Ford, Corydon L. (Box 33)
  - Female Students
    - Andrews, Lucy C.. (Box 33)
    - Bellis, Ida M.. (Box 33)
    - Eaglesfield, Bessie. (Box 33)
    - Ekin, A.W.. (Box 33)
    - Farrand, Helen M.. (Box 33)
    - Foster,Vine C.. (Box 33)
    - Freeman, Alice E.. (Box 33)
    - Mason, Gertrude H.. (Box 33)
    - Reed, Louisa. (Box 33)
    - Salmon, Lucy M.. (Box 33)
    - Stockbridge, Emma S.. (Box 33)
    - Williams, Mary A.. (Box 33)
  - Male Students
    - Allen, DeWitt C.. (Box 33)
    - Alexander, Henry W.. (Box 33)
    - Baker, George S. (Box 33)
    - Barry, Edmund O. (Box 33)
    - Blair, Charles A. (Box 33)
    - Boone, Philip R. (Box 33)
    - Brown, Clarence S. (Box 33)
    - Burt, William W. (Box 33)
    - Cable, Ben T. (Box 33)
    - Caldwell, James O. (Box 33)
    - Campbell, Burton B. (Box 33)
    - Campbell, Henry M. (Box 33)
- 1876 Class Album
  - Professors
    - Angell, James B. (Box 34)
    - Frieze, Henry (Box 34)
    - Morris, George S. (Box 34)
    - Cocker (Box 34)
    - Olney (Box 34)
    - Taylor (Box 34)
    - Adams (Box 34)
    - Harrington, Mark W. (Box 34)
    - Merriam, Geo. B. (Box 34)
    - Scott (Box 34)
    - Hutchins, Harry B. (Box 34)
    - Blackburn, Frank (Box 34)
    - Denison, Charles S. (Box 34)
  - Students
    - Andrews, Lucy Caroline (Box 34)
    - Bellis, Ida M. (Box 34)
    - Brown, Clarence Shepard (Box 34)
    - Burt, William Wadsworth (Box 34)
    - Cable, Ben (Box 34)
    - Campbell, Henry Monroe (Box 34)
    - De Wolf, Anson Peter (Box 34)
    - Eaglesfield, Bessie (Box 34)
    - Ekin, Annie Warden (Box 34)
    - Farrand, Helen Marie (Box 34)
    - Foster, Vine (Box 34)
    - Freeman, Alice Elvira (Box 34)
    - Gustin, Fred Keays (Box 34)
    - Mapel, John J. (Box 34)
    - Mason, Gertrude H. (Box 34)
    - Pearson, Albert Chesterfield (Box 34)
    - Reed, Louisa Maria (Box 34)
    - Safely, Ben (Box 34)
    - Salmon, Lucy Maynard (Box 34)
    - Smith, Howard Burnham (Box 34)
    - Stanley, Louis Crandall (Box 34)
    - Steere, Joseph Hall (Box 34)
    - Stockbridge, Emma Sophia (Box 34)
    - Varlo, Olaf (Box 34)
    - Volland, Albert Jacob (Box 34)
    - Walker, Bryant (Box 34)
    - Williams, Mary Alice (Box 34)
- 1878 Class Album
  (Annie Peck Album)
  (bound in 3 vols.)
  - Faculty
    - Adams, Charles Kendall (Box 35)
      [1-8]
    - Angell, James Burrill (Box 35)
      [1-1]
    - Beman, Wooster Woodruff (Box 35)
      [1-17]
    - Cocker, Rev. Benjamin Franklin (Box 35)
      [1-4]
    - Demmon, Isaac Newton (Box 35)
      [1-20]
    - Denison, Charles Simeon (Box 35)
      [1-19]
    - DePont, Paul Rousseau (Box 35)
      [1-21]
    - D'Ooge, Rev. Martin Luther (Box 35)
      [1-5]
    - Frieze, Henry Simmons (Box 35)
      [1-3]
    - Greene, Charles Ezra (Box 35)
      [1-11]
    - Hennequin, Alfred (Box 35)
      [1-22]
    - Jones, Charles Nelson (Box 35)
      [1-18]
    - Jones, Elisha (Box 35)
      [1-14]
    - Langley, John Williams (Box 35)
      [1-10]
    - Morris, George Sylvester (Box 35)
      [1-9]
    - Olmey, Edward (Box 35)
      [1-6]
    - Pattengill, Albert Henderson (Box 35)
      [1-16]
    - Pettee, William Henry (Box 35)
      [1-12]
    - Steere, Joseph Beale (Box 35)
      [1-13]
    - Tyler, Moses Coit (Box 35)
    - Walter, Edward Lorraine (Box 35)
      [1-15]
    - Williams, Rev. George Palmer (Box 35)
      [1-2]
  - Class
    - Abell, Walter Scott (Box 37)
      [3-18]
    - Allen, Daniel Ayres (Box 37)
      [3-1]
    - Allen, Marion Benjamin (Box 37)
      [3-2]
    - Allmendinger, George Franklin (Box 37)
      [3-19]
    - Angell, Alexis Caswell (Box 36)
      [2-1]
    - Arey, Clarence Oliver (Box 37)
      [3-20]
    - Augur, Walter Wheaton (Box 36)
      [2-2]
    - Barbour, Florus Alonzo (Box 36)
      [2-3]
    - Bary, Minnie (Box 36)
      [2-4]
    - Benneson, Cora Agnes (Box 36)
      [2-5]
    - Butts, William Henry (Box 36)
      [2-6]
    - Byrd, Mary Emma (Box 36)
      [2-7]
    - Chandler, Eva (Box 36)
      [2-8]
    - Colby, June Rose (Box 36)
      [2-9]
    - Cook, Webster (Box 36)
      [2-10]
    - Cooley, Charles Malcom (Box 37)
      [3-4]
    - Danaher, Michael Buchanan (Box 36)
      [2-11]
    - Daugherty, Charles M. (Box 36)
      [2-12]
    - DeTar, David Noble (Box 36)
      [2-13]
    - DuShane, James Dick (Box 37)
      [3-21]
    - Edwards, John Herbert (Box 37)
      [3-5]
    - Fleming, Randall Wade (Box 36)
      [2-14]
    - Garner, Charles Edwin (Box 37)
      [3-6]
    - Garrison, Franklin (Box 36)
      [2-15]
    - Gayley, Charles Mills (Box 36)
      [2-16]
    - Griggs, Clarence (Box 36)
      [2-17]
    - Grove, William Van (Box 37)
      [3-22]
    - Hanson, John Ellery (Box 37)
      [3-23]
    - Hanus, Paul Henry (Box 37)
      [3-12]
    - Harrower, George Hatfield (Box 36)
      [2-18]
    - Hinckley, Watson Dexter (Box 37)
      [3-7]
    - Horton, George (Box 36)
      [2-19]
    - Hubbard, Edward King (Box 36)
      [2-20]
    - Jenks, Jeremiah Whipple (Box 36)
      [2-21]
    - Jenks, William Lee (Box 36)
      [2-22]
    - Johnson, John Butler (Box 37)
      [3-24]
    - Johnson, William Claflin (Box 37)
      [3-8]
    - Josenhans, Timothy (Box 37)
      [3-25]
    - Judd, Henry Wick (Box 37)
      [3-26]
    - Knight, George Wells (Box 36)
      [2-23]
    - Mann, Eugene George (Box 37)
      [3-27]
    - Moore, William Van (Box 36)
      [2-24]
    - Morse, Seymour Tenny (Box 37)
      [3-28]
    - Myers, Horace Greeley (Box 37)
      [3-13]
    - Myrick, Harry Pierce (Box 36)
    - Norton, Albert James (Box 37)